

Member Technical Staff seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Business Analysis, Solution

Architecture, PL/SQL, Python, Java, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, C, C++, JS, SQL



Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Total Experience: 1 Year(s) 3 Month(s)

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computer Science and

Maintenance Engineering]

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Member Technical Staff, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application

Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, Business Analysis, Solution

Architecture, PL/SQL, Python, Java, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, C, C++, JS, SQL

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Summary

Experienced Software Developer with skills that include an end to end application development, analytical thinking and creative problem-solving. Able to apply customer service concepts to IT to improve the user experience for clients, employees and administration.

Work Experience

Metric Stream Infotech as Member Technical Staff Apr 2019 to Jul 2020

Member Technical Staff

Metricstream as Member Technical Staff -Java Apr 2019 to Jul 2020

Working for regulating DMS and Survey libraries according to Client requirement using Javascript as front-end application and Oracle 11g background.

Hands-on experience in debugging PL/SQL queries.

Created Reports, Forms, and Dashboard, Blueprint, Workflow from

Worked on triggering emails and Workflows.

Managed customers' expectations of support and technology functionality in order to provide a positive user experience.

Infosys as Systems Engineer Jan 2019 to Apr 2019

Applied web development, database handling and Shell scripting.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science and Engineering) from Maharaja Surajmal Institute of Technology (MSIT)-GGSIPU, New Delhi in 2018

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last	Used	Experience
PL/SQL			
Python			
Java,			
HTML, CSS			
BOOTSTRAP			
C, C++			
JS			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
German				

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time

Work Authorization